tim is the stimulation because that's
depressing
that this family gave such a good talk
about the squall Casteneda touch them
about how to select so anyways it's a
little Toshiba libretto I kind of wanted
to take alarm and break
yeah he'll talk about your data for to
go back to that explanation
yes of course abuse of course but she
says ninety was not redo the flora with
him that's all of course I'd like to
continue still and 3hd
watch over some things we're talking
about in each course a chunk of Aurelia
of custom course that's in one thing
Stan you but no I mean we're talking
about flow we're talk why did the course
come virtual idea of course adjusted
regime after but you're these positions
the challenge of the bottom little boy
hamesha Muhammad Allah yeah which is of
the five Geisha topics and which is that
cm yes that's cool okay poor watch TV ad
Avenu scholar we should talk about the
content a little bit each open content
you should remember ago I really
remember yeah which great book those
courses have a get her that if any
processbook say it minguk Miami
yes the data there's no crab is nyan
regimen which commentary you okay let's
do that now though I was looking over
the course yes ma'am yeah thinking
course martini it's very interesting
miniatures flow private session to
photocopies pgbilic yourself which one
gets of course there are you know
which and I said it was your school
school in case you die elimination is
will show you
that's Lucia's living amid oh it's a
marginal motion it's pretty much the
branch of you know when I'm your class
ability recent model is a is a question
Richard theta and that's pretty typical
graduated from Michael see what you did
again she'll ever master leo marinade
oceany so how do you arrange the order
so de minimis by dad the girl good
in it did you much can Yahoo the lady by
someone there's nothing abuse me and I
put it in the document because that's
the one journey yesterday as a question
because I know but I must uh we're gonna
try to finish no but that I'm six that
quenches terms so is that really can't
say it about
wada you will have all the possible it's
a political I see I can see all this
information of the whole structure
doctora
okay the first thing the advantage is
the 75 pages famous abet string its text
all of really customize the got serviced
my tray and addictive awesome secretary
secretary Oh a son get yesterday's night
Saturday story started about depression
or are five great books of my trail
that's I believe my three this one we
studied first the etymology a machete
Arabic you can call by the way which of
the five topics the guy is a crispity
channel protecting wisdom number four
such as the mother stands
Ginty or Turkish Cola
my only focus has none yet
Laura memory had stayed in cities in
there is nice it easily wasn't far off
from my murmurs excitedly gasps Thank
You Tasha some of my sister we studied
that and the way I described it is now
wrote this course versus Hamlet
brushless doubly and the pathology of
course I kinda understood away yeah
right the perfection of wisdom when you
my okok besides okay these are some
other state scriptures they are
misleading foods dorchen chakra to be
the same a high enough sage so changing
but you sattva chromia yeah except a
correct
totally correct presentation empty
chrome absolutely push never be stained
your pasta to versus tell Noah we
persevered 930 some of this buzzer
buzzer Bishop Adorama's not digitally
lower middle way music is in the woods
the gazelles the first 90 on the piece
and the acceleration bull days worth to
the such name everyone recording here
he's just hanging out you know I'm
Preston and he's waiting until people
have enough seats for him to come back I
reckon at the Buddhist bottoms up for
Cowell is a business mogul Samantha burn
smoke pretty and he's close young
blueskins quite a pretty odd
everything's closed so anyway that body
of literature at the Patel and it's it
at the same 12 user when they give
advice do not sit less Petrucelli as a
touch to be always attractive
monetary-ism normally memorize it before
the permanence it's tiny it's a
the doll was a stupid minutes later and
it's cute the kids go out on them at the
Milliken dates in 12 colleges room as
the assets quality charge the VHS
premarital agreement Jessie recorded mom
[Music]
you finance an image that is cute pretty
good choice 38 you can't take a nap
right old mother string you buy the most
part about the venomous but I must still
have someone city safe it not still a
basic Christian that it's a customer no
it's awesome because it that way so
Guevara Mexican man through the Tavor
stupid became a global solution a
solution your mantras depressed otaku
permit a seminary coverage which in
short custom of series which if
committed solution
that's a Stalag is a setting on the
right is private empty so he's been
mooching apostasy though it's a theory
you sure what not because it Natasha
Tobin Cockburn it's private Virginia
Blue Star Kachina diet fantastic me just
cook voice ooh ChaCha yeah
entering the middle way by chandrakirti
which is a great commentary on Thursday
never sit in the boat
ver technique yesterday revenue yes
Lomonosov commentary cut through my
sponsor huge a Grom lay its pyramid
watch it yet 4,000 pages at the sort of
this extraneous commentary i'd never
offered a monetary card ominous
customers theist spy commentary yeah
which the community divided one is
called children's gotta searches you
didn't miss overview of them it doesn't
change the result of tsavorite
inopportune then Surf temperature it's
got its attention means
analysis at the analyst and both books
are always written in debate style or
bikini cannabis in the comedy material
still a Cogburn sport at the cost of
food available ginika this mean years
which are mr. champ the first 12 years
get a message yet what can you do so
much that I got on the and then this to
go after all that which is written
important man widget area coordinator
try to but don't know what she doesn't
answer it I challenge just become a
better smarter facility ever talk about
competitive group incredibly beautiful
it's never I advocacy with nickimja
doesn't if it's deputy Vista co-founder
was it free maneuver at la crise
awakening and there are Indian
commentary we use those no way listen
now puts it aside from the to monastic
Hiromi minajesty texture from explosion
kako da Mucha some coppice
gamba itself perhaps so if you're out
there if you're a good student yesterday
yesterday verdict what studio is not a
sister you're not you don't just study
when you prostitute about you throw in
no but I show you some copies
explanation is a browser based units and
capitals illumination a table the truth
of what did what did negara not really
mean what the Cherokee Stella Stella
gasps that's the Americanization team
which are thinning that we just reached
halfway 11 pages so far pages when we
finish in five years
okay and that's some coppers ultimate at
the absolute need sometimes most time
there's not time to study it carefully
the BA kua I request
specialized oh yeah Brazil somebody's a
chain yet never is my script your
teacher Miss Annie
we spent eight years on it wasn't let
potentially meta and we started with
four or five of my friends and they
alter the potentially negatively charged
the same both provide useful eek in my
serum or Costner he's an incredible
teacher okay so that's middle way
editors in the bush and we spent two
years I don't got an IV Nile two years
undeniable and here number 17 and year
number 18
God's units to Brazil nuts it but maybe
nine of the main group drafts thinnest
Ginga which is not a sutra Vinaya Sutra
it's written I think yes will threaten a
piece of the chilla Viacom guna part of
its very good enough about so we study
it from gonna Papa and again every
monastery a bomb
compassion upon the study it's about
them go buddy don't say which dumps cuz
it's Doug Dom means a summary as a poem
and you memorize it
okay tip of so mr. Spinella the Superman
idea Allison is translating what a does
she's translating the shortest possible
one I just avoid in theory but usually
daddy no now okay
so and if you really want to go into it
raise your man yesterday a shock
absorbers III is a shop will go back a
commentary which is module exam which is
a little news festival commentaries and
some emotions started to translate it
here is little bit about these days
there's a does they get and they took
all the recordings in there
the silicon vigil missed some noise
Rochelle is a browser to that position
but that anybody's this is now the vinai
isn't a question come in your mind
Minaya until were a year 17 young
greater story now and when you do some
that cycle Gordon you know and use a
chest 253 pounds per fully ordained
month to charge this 264 for this simple
9 to 10 years in the monster before they
learn their vows but emerges in that
state there's no supreme simply listed
but of course I get the engine yeah
there's a belly gets a bursa of York
again again lemons yet again isn't the
change a house teacher because they've
definitely she takes poor nature would
rush in young age can teach the kids to
put their duties which is just our open
the device that we should I didn't
Minister the other kids in the same room
under former centimeter which is
testable bit below you'd be believe the
key okay the Ballet's new course thank
you ninotchka Berlin I need a boy so sex
care of them
he feeds for Roberto car meets the
change them it is their marks is there a
bit controversial in addition to the
butcher editorials
by personally that's Kasavin mom is
substantial but when ambient then break
about this idea that I didn't notice the
reason she said Beatrice was worthless I
mean yes agency in yeah boo child was a
better the world she's attacked out
commentary on this puzzle - best
commentary Katerina Savalas saw so no
say so no corrected so lava
he wrote a 2,000 page commentary on them
it is just commentary can I be
a man - a man - Junior urias new
commentary thoughts on supplemental in
May Charlie Draghi studied sir on cardio
it's an incredible company variety
commentary I suppose - disease
yeah yeah it is a child investable of
greece's things before we ah go I got
shot there are several heavy shadow it
was a rancher then amongst us menachem
doctorates its Alicia the premier and
study turned her before they became a
former
Malloy Disney few charitable deed is
done much longer dice put a most which
is self a series of I'm Samantha
Deutscher the kabocha chase both Manasa
in Chester yep tomorrow is total
question at the Gordon gets a quarter
what is your brush without which is
inequality tauros tauros Kasavin
Angelica Morgan is against this possible
si mi link Amanda she's a child mr.
Emerson
being a last name is Rover I can't press
the bro assets British Argonauts at the
protest I bet I'm not the Cheetahs goal
of a snail cannot disturb the yaneemango
nobody watch em longer the key
driver can't really write unique in the
besides yes never suit rissalah zener
estrade cameo that it there was a
pharmacist when you intervene I am
bottom extremist no Gordo revenue versus
83 of mr. sneaky to the calanques shake
the original incident
important idea PRV enthusiam so it's
condemned we provide services academic
mountain in a shy legislature session
Romero
with just a more noble impetus control
because that Bullock old conventional
people device 0 but that's the choice
Liang Shan that I feel say intersection
and is non-starter
no mr. justice can you get no is a man
that the buzzy
but advisor Postma trades lockable a
story yes Lee which is understand yet
spawn sure that the possibility yes my
supremacy just toy buzzing like
temperatures
yeah Malcolm ninety the change this is
the quantum Milan stronger protectionist
accordion Corsica to apologize are in
many ways the information formats a
bullet torch century but I mostly have
separate video but it by success through
Amina is no stop thousands people
cooking attracting younger put a video
be sure mm-hmm
I like to tell stories on a plane one
time yeah some I know it's a Virginia
and Obama below nobility similar to
cutter genius now this money you gotta
do Camilla Talia I was in the army yeah
bit of a celibate dad wall in that
period I spent 12 years yeah that's it
but I broke the mold I mean you did that
much that's the shoulder chest yeah put
the gradient line Chicago and Brokaw
called
and in eboo discuss out yams kazoo
started Tibetan
next to me you know I didn't see Biscay
monoxide insomnia is now Toyota we were
flying in a hurry
you want to Cazale surprise yeah Oh give
yourself and then I had I thought our
very cool plan yeah put it on one page
the yellow shows try me Suki butakov are
you voting about it if you drink
yes Liberty story coca-cola squall
Cunard no driving Cooper mistake no
capital he doesn't say don't drink when
is cousin because I'll me otherwise I
see that would estimate don't call
yourself my Student Union is / - no
cheating having my usually kid whatever
it is knowing in this device is better
my intercom yes the volunteers and oh
yeah the show to watch me about my
service at the stranger to get you a new
piggy my gosh I might be Dharma mania
that dragon
okay not okay Sonia Beatrice kaiser
gives - gosh : that's it yet we do have
Adama give no service at the Mozilla
mama Dharma is a champ okay basically in
for Madame Delambre bless Judas lama
team and it keeps coming up evil 3 of
let's say you're given whether some
people change but should those are
Biederman's a bit of a mission that's it
let but no I'm here 1991 as I said they
go through the chassis of him tell you
at the time yes cousin brothers took a
demon less than 10 major diss demonic
immersion classes the notes are it's
kind of weird
is the nurse is not the stranded but
that was nice you know and you know what
they don't know the extraneous now the
battery is useful but I must assume
that's it let's ignore this
resonator stove the technical back to
the eastern annual Chilean desert sands
when your college 72 divided into
classes this mastery is easy and fun
Raza if it meant them in the brain man I
need your class appreciation or chest
Anisha class today I didn't want their
connection is thought about we went
class mobile mobile in history class in
maybe they pretty well in good because
there was nobody to debate with a
personable and yes conservative it's
both civic petticoat or a stylist with
pushed in there in a classic West Coast
apropos steely there no supposed to
serve or examiner yes a suti later no
but she's have hole in their knowledge
because no doubt yes you yes I get a
drink your verse 90s but almost is
beautiful still a mother stay up
corporate administrator okay
Buddhist logic but it's color if you're
thinking ok that's just that it's so
important I am Vanessa misciagna it's so
important I thought you boys know every
year as the god you but supremist
not three mates of certain elements
another city of seven a groupie we eat
judges to church Britt met phenomenon
very thorough scholar okay so this
column as more Cherokee Chandi their
majestic
making this job because I'm figure you
should do it I don't want you to
embarrass me with yeah I just / - camped
by the way
cominius virtual and zero is a girl now
spear Candela is singapura no Baloch in
the bra is della buttress I shake the
bubble tofu tofu has either a tofu of
yes the high temperature Madonna's
during the tomorrow photo a Bordeaux
charity I'm watching from work yeah
English because any water okay and I was
amazing then after that we mix them in
Bosnia Thomas mishali at the sausage
learn heard them report
yeah that's up she took a bite I almost
a abbreviate oh yes Dudley yeah he's
like its turquoise quirky the province
and the rock I hope what I guess my
closure and you Wizards appetites may
look of the famous case history of very
good teaching and Hiroshi instrument
liver Cheney but you can repeat what a
pathetic this is Russ to people that
they should mix stop losing about
Kadam he privation special it's the snow
is still backward thought of course need
a Stuyvesant of the scenes try to
connect it was let us say Denise ever
that the boy seems a stems much more
power a the local boy Liam much they do
- Anya anytime you can come up with some
kind of curse there's grow a the cool
girl pre don't wait I gotta believe
there is exactly the bar shows arrange
it Allah it is not cover school Torah
you know
you have your own you know Finland
Finland you I don't know anything about
Friday's 620 be able to line teens much
as you know that my stomach's laid
that's the thumb because here's
something you wish I'd say it was a
smooth emulate adrift in urk
yeah we made a plan sure
nope Academy little bulldog stuff happen
everyone go Alex and military first
native ocean if Sarah's no Ellen you
know if you really need a window Thomas
Cavalli's to Maddux the child is there
will you stop because I pitch when you
lose the yes sir do you do know
Elizabeth Lane is the channel but is
there any new using it there's a toy yes
a winner here
21 to 25 okay you know some pathetic
words make the greatest against courses
Novartis it was periods and you might
mistake or higher yes they're very shy
it's a biting Apple II wish but recorder
but - that's but that much the year's
squad could guess from what purposes is
what my own monastery at the box so it's
negation about the progression people
died I needed piccata
kotomi right epitome so you cannot talk
about no you shouldn't they document the
book and change if you worst apologize
butter layer three excited if I'd seen a
boy episode where she notices Geshe
given us live Sikhism examined pretty SF
cm ministerial knowledge
devar koala just said the bad quality
showed back when Geoghan death
the same quality you have to appear the
baseerat slamming but there must be a me
Muslim but it's so without much notice
almost me sure against your honor
because it's for example I'm listening
sir what about it must be answer me
angry okay that's it that's a typical
period it's a their videos Welker
first look at Auto much digital cannot
get them touched your permissions right
this Turkish culture these are topics
from topic but the Chairman is jamming
our chat area okay Sanga he mentions the
1200 cover it odd minutes is vania
service mysterious reason is that this
it's lawful if Sean and so there's a
custom yes previous I did say is bleep
right it's here Astro chicken in the
besides hello quinoa but not charge of
course nutshell is a village juice from
soaked in a stadium customized by Mary
Cheney Vista you said Acosta get the
juice out of summarize the church story
is my dream that certainly yes that
agenda for the King circle by your
monastery and some money I raise a child
on this monomial Turkish has nine yet
one of them is called some soup but on
which is my incidence at the time scuba
diver
as soon as Dakota's I release my Prakash
Danian Vinod since menu
he showed nicely had done and initial
Commission all the possible service
wasn't it can be not saved if
orientations like suppose you are
Hinayana for I was nervous in a yahoo
paraphernalia and then you graduate to
Mahayana but don't be on e 20 parts is
the key chest but the time my mom I know
carted that guy that would I just hit
though these books were missing yeah
interested static need to build a potato
master machinist area to change to the
devalued civilization in the second yeah
belong missing and you believe potato
crazy break raising a shoulders Russia
but I see her burden you busting IBM in
put them and that was the first version
of internet that ability Arabic yoga cat
or a cuddly boo-boo on a mature tana na
computer a tibia in the world
what's a miracle it was the two volumes
that we have a copy in yes the yes but
if Cydonia the country I mean yes mr.
polecat what relations that recently
this is a little note is name address or
better to put Bobo it happens everywhere
I Atma so that as the bush if you are
waiting for your yes it was
dismemberment yes but how do you
classify pause and do Tony interference
is what they said as many thoughts in
circles ok there's a sort of course
esthetician in every year cash they go
ahead for three months Savoy three
missing some ideological is it Chinese
history adopt anybody at the Virginie
Mesnard method there was a custom yes
brevich cartridge itself to beta
every year his daughter Bacardi what a
gene Mesa the monastery would select
monastery with variety said lucha
candidate the flag national of israel
glasses busy set it the Russian
commander did you buy a backpack you
obsess about I do yell it are you John
yeah just when I stood John it's a
special man I want a state money came on
the study molested Rivera and they were
debate together but you don't mister or
not changing my sensitization we do you
do all night
the virus generator is a plan with so
much when you speak that kind of like
the Olympics ethically Biscay agree
sorry battery or 3 month / mysterious
table with surf Susie Cheney inanimate
dream is it's a virus it's a packet of
crackers in one month next but that it's
a that's which stuff it doesn't you see
I mean person XD but it's very rare to
go to one which is Slava brilliant ideas
new eyes it youngja diligent didn't
bragging young masters Petronas told the
teacher I'm going I don't care what you
do I put that much - yes cuz I was your
age I don't know what's Korean is not
every ya go her so I was like unofficial
thirsty elephant if it suddenly
disappeared of a burger and I found
there and I'm happy I did it yeah -
there was that much that I had a big
breakthrough yep on yellow minion ok
well practically
it was extremely but Jared I know she
asian boy straight to jail I was very
frustrated
yeah we should I guarantee I lost half
of my students
tenacity course preferred of the your
Kia vehicle potato although you
historic student officially it's hard
it's a slower than that Orton I decided
I'm gonna and yet it's so star you know
that something you instead the stuff
that number to figure this out you know
so don't be a friend
boys about neatest over the difficult
subject surcharge this large never met
and I became one of the path yes though
idealist I'm a florist but I must a yeah
I remember being yeah Polina cocky our
Chin's Nilsson either sir just do it
okay okay okay that's the years I'm
sorry Spencer modernity at godís a
genius wouldn't put it okay I'd like to
cover a few more courses you show but of
course at number five course of play
John yeah a bad karma tota tiny bit
scary to me Academy taught separately
where the vast lava CinemaScore so fast
and I said my gosh the chill away
occurred about casca but the most
dangerous case on Oprah karma kid is yes
West festival slowest car Louisiana
bottom had ever given offense as much
much cheaper at last discovered and no
but when you wear with absolutely no my
equal to in Western culture Westerners
yes a burner contain mostly Americans
since the war Americans are fairly
European America I thought I should
almost oh yeah there's no cigar sadhana
the Bible's stop academies d'Italia
karma in in America the Americans will
die Jaros I remember my mom yeah bonus
for mom I remember the
first time I heard the word karma could
they have better in those years you take
a dog listen last night I was a stuff I
cut the 1950s okay this is doing so
spits out they hear the word first
wasn't elusive little Cadmus add the
cuffs you heard about it and he's not
like mama but I was killing so hard the
Yelp Duvall's record oh I miss my mom
Imams cuz I'll new give I'm on you're
gonna put your mark on my karma and I'm
like where's Becca yeah go to the Copa
had gotten back to you know boys at
Kadena financier
it's just bad karma the high karma you
know like mothers don't have some mini
grocer that's where most Americans comic
Fiesta lalu its interpreted in the
Carmel never just one of the cans of
food a sampler seminar say it's like a
big boomerang Lou cigarettes totally
melt cutter approach it is Mars just
about success with machetes you have all
these several I made a list
yeah the Rasta money stadium look at the
key we do it we look at the key you
should she's got for you got a UH Manoa
right Sherwood Stanek exhibit in
interviewed mr. president first invaded
with a mr. mom my very Twitter so and by
the way yes sir when there's no
mustaches a near to him when you put in
the hole he's gonna talk about that
tonight
you know just like this avoided my
decision so you know that's kind of one
of the big reasons I thought nice I'm a
bunch of fish in fish monastic or chorus
at that point because but I'm mostly
close this is such a new coffee
Symphony monument independent alia and
I'm very proud of how I got rid since of
course somehow karma world the caribou
that karma gives all the details about
at the diner karma yeah it's touched me
you know I'll be done of course epidemic
washa stand there we use heavily and we
or she said he wasn't a spoil Suleiman
welcome through Betty Turner llama they
show comes teddy bear Dalai Lama bit
better Dalai Lama and episode momentary
parish a commentary on Bolivia common
some caribou startup Chile recomm this
is yesterday's for the grassy you are
the images for the Swiss is not secure
so I like them
and the Sulak
and he's got a the most uh okay sure
my life of needs are we secure message
me and anyway we are allowed to not have
hair up here most nourished above all
was near below was this would no one
does want to us so I used yeah at this
point so how to find a pastor Iverson I
see it dress under the bus this book by
the way is the best excited the kanga
would be a graph has sank up so
immediate no more yes the hadith is not
bush bloom actually noted I suppose to
least it's acute event is the castle
magnets big because my child but
ambushed at Thomas you knock arsenic
it's based on fifteen yeah Tampa dances
finicky hook fifteen busy finishing it
knots Italy atyminius in oil mm besides
yes they were hot it is not frozen cup
forest welcome you know I hope you don't
make it a coffee table book yeah yeah
coverage de Blasio to not a famous
toilets for because the risk and avocado
combining a dome atop gravity
his machete tradition ministerial
my mama took Nico of candy covalent
Akito neeraj Dania the Pascal was not
crazy
was Chris Anya what doesn't resemble a a
Scotty assume oh no as Muslim at was
Christian yet chromatic just open up
close your eyes that's that Croatia
Croatia Gaza in a piece of lasagna with
a carriage it'sa are you carving it
disappear so ich Kenne didn't do okay
course number six hey course shakes a
challenge Erik Alma's mcgrann chicken it
was 90 beretta this has an interesting
story behind it interesting story states
any and it's fun to tell you the story
in chestnuts fabric as America cannabis
elective course I do not study the
Charlie so avenues which I saw traumas
mcgrann check of universities it results
come stairs on covering the knee chest
critical acclaim
you know what about shorted share
vanished or any other news a child but
sister Augustine years of childhood
traumas dementia can you explain your
solution in knowing is channel I think I
told you the story yeah don't stop
discuss on the story we yeah usual
managua leave community ministry empty
list a monogamist was the bully man
means we chapter chapter knowledge at
houses huzi laborda mom they're giving
Tuesday is the first day yeah the
barrage a back time for you sir we use
his commentary
we study the Dharma get pretty much
that's it let's hear a public about yeah
so those lamar labid are my yet cuz
evidence left me as annual whatever
gives new york cheated is just a car
didn't because i can't i can't have to
sleep at the month but i was to get
mastered a you go for shut down which
means a new shaft an order to or to give
the mosrite some prayers of waited a
two-mile it away any remember you tell
me the month love it understand everyone
side that for something you know if you
don't have any but I was still mother
over the Hoda it was a poor
community it was a poor bit Nicaragua so
it was exciting for the month to get
some money and buy years ago EMF say
yesterday you're supposed to recite
something every budget that's in
Mongolia diamond cutter surgeries
grandsheikh 800 chin you know what she
said there I think in China or the list
of cadet Osama your knee of Jotunheimen
so anyway we would recite the diamond
cutter Sutra we put the children so
traumas McGregor body
Moya bar and we'll high gravity watching
the sake yes yeah Mongolian memory
whiskey and he has a palm heel and then
he would take a diamond cutter suitor
William to the family's house on the
Sutro love to eat much Adama in fact he
died with a role in his mouth Oh Sheila
biggest exciting to know love died with
raw here couscous a low point you can go
ahead he sat there like this for like
five minutes but that good idea to
change so you can really buy anywhere
it was hard to get the doughnut
witnesses
so he loved to eat so he said younger
idiot let's split the scripture out the
second lunch faster separate them to
understand the movement we must remember
of course mr. indeed sir
this cutting fingers that's yeah but I
see ants project ability best commentary
difficult guides in Taiwan the
percentage of pathology on the level but
Lama Stanley and he's a great writer
although Scottish besides around their
common let us say commentary question
touchable is a live commentary
commentary today and we're answering it
avoidable yeah that was it exact
opposite of strands and there's a short
common it is karate commentary and
robust Ubuntu it's only 30 pages 32
string is shorter than the staccato a
sham so terrible anyway something
interesting happen my personal nama
question seriousness to chose my Alicia
nila McCann in the chair yeah what's
this one's a Benilde doctors doctors
gazelle story malicious office itself
was pathetic misses me and I didn't have
a always said courses Duvall I thought
I'd show with vegetable dramas this was
our team there's nothing to have a
process so I I started translating yes
top it arises but I'm of patellas how I
always remember the stalker Kiev sit
down
yes the cutaways project approval but
Auckland
don't watch discuss liberal lunch leave
a hospital okay those are the two at the
bar or if you wanna make a good story
for you sorry
everyone needs emptiness much-discussed
oh yes you try the shoe store
salmon does not post atados iboga is
residential by Satan and the total
shopping channel before you go too far
very time the quest is critical is
course I have a good a possible a
my emptiness bushes reason they put this
post on toy 24 sets in of course this is
a block or so percent chance Horace I
don't remember that's a good party oh
yeah you're right there are some prison
but they're lower midline diastema
initiatives in the road and some of them
are also used by the earth raise new
taxes or anyways so it's good to have a
good dose of diamond educator at the
port rubbish a reddish Evangelic courier
capital my homework and vanadium flashy
[Music]
we also found a carving of Tony Lama in
Russia those initially you may not know
Tony Lamanna see John's team his night
sister come on the Jonah my brain
chitinous live level of science
facilitate cancer they spent 14 years
instead they just made daily catalog I
need a Shoshone piteously we and our
friends can get that together it's good
if so oh that's that the publicist del
I tablets can hear about it from don't
wanna Sochi long accustomed huh we have
to try to say in case there's a fire
there something Russians love to smoke
it was killing with great is that you
know tonight the notre dad burn oh so I
didn't of them got it so it things
happen fires fires happen but I switch
out some anyway so we we had we got
permission to go into the library and
when we can ask Buddhist machine debates
you know that second family
oh it's a good thing is it overly uh
thinking because there is so look Tigers
just cut the like yes this is searching
there's a special search key yes
potentially search for torrenuova
one card leash and turn allow me yes
supports into the stone that was made
and I would get Tim it's in your it's in
the it's in your manual annoying those
carvings all look the same to be honest
it's you say this monkey would be
significant before the sounded a bit of
course there was a bit of Sangha was
with the Savannah anyway under the
carving it says this is time I was bored
this one comes guys understood that
trial I went through a bullet I think it
might be kind of the his hat Tony you
are ok ok and as you know next to me
you can just scroll down calm as you
know that course became the diamond
cutter because I said that good stuff
business community such as its Betsy as
a confident enough I think it's
interesting that they say talking uni
and then that kind of started this er
social nutshell Gladys is a say mmm ok
I'm gonna do two more yogurts in the
reminder I don't care yesterday law I'm
just being polite
a trusted Esther
employment okay mmm what's course seven
course course same Bodhisattva vows bit
uppity subject I was trying to find him
pay anything for it yeah because it nice
to do something about but I just lost
nurse Miller getting a shawl this is
Chandra gummy I think I want me he lived
around there oh no no 680 except Tina's
not a monk she saw that she was not she
don't a I never won a flamin mouth
which many of you have recorded them is
a lie better be sattva also we have
mouth from doctor yes every thought load
the Buddha other sources this course
Adam course I'm sorry our Sangha San
Agustin ever undergone me for that just
serious touched for the 64 but Chinese
friends Kotori and asked John I think
John to him which itself kid died 46 46
sir chest 64 total yes - did of civil if
so what couldn't I bet the chase six
secondary bells you know many other
associated valve commitments nobody
should give her there there's a book on
the business on copy device worship with
deputies under I used that for the vows
in many business cars they appeared many
pages
longest-reigning ambient scriptures
unless his collects a summer version
collection yet another bachata Nizam she
died technically just be a yes was
mercifully to know that
commercially put with his hat on Canada
channel Junction Shimla Shimla Shimla
means highway so Lamas not shared with
supporters nobody said we use that place
wasn't looking good tip it again
due to the kindness over speciality
there's an incredible yes that is true
north of ice season see I should regard
honesty it's by against from inferior
monastery called Obama does not with the
Kimia on Bella Dimas and Dalai Lama he
decided to write a publishing the
besides can you go thumbs a beard is
good as a dog so don't assume means
three in a Buddha a bit a bit better
stop or diversity tip of amira and then
second but he said to my decision
you know explain okay on short cut okay
as we talked about when everybody blah
blah says here's your thoughts on my
suits a better correctly
completely but shortly I bet quite a
couple of students one is like 3,000
cars the material is hurting because the
ownership pci beatification scared it
I'm sorting a bit of he wrote this
masala to me location very many but I
have no can you go very precise watching
torch know watching sin about valve we
should all misty
I taught it here at Diamond Mountain
during the three-year retreat
yeah piti piti village in a bit chilly
aims to change data by the way that was
an extremely yeah that I guess Virginia
but that teaching with it it's a Cheney
ability imagining if you can get her
emotions every store yeah so much that
is changing but I was very happy yellow
shoes so anyway we found half of his
book when Ashley Palladino evoke me you
don't have two pages Paula Venus ty
needs and then we spent years in court
appearances the were stubborn bastards
90s that know every spell astray needs
and the context turns without prayer
focus dragon and Ashley Chatham best
range they expect um and we put it
together
Haley John Brady here by the general
agent
[Applause]
so I'm a difficult body something else I
took floors me i betta butta set for ya
I'm celibacy waters in Capernaum
pristine what school Kokoschka
yeah higher middle way environment I met
the police at religious reason input one
more course then we'll go to the class
I'm sure I'm gonna be in the money put
my home site is my church you know if
God wills until yesterday yeah I was
wasn't I sure wasn't related to the
Sanskrit the word wish comes from that
Jelani are so dropped out okay anyway
here we go
of course a it wasn't them one of the
more popular smear the next course was
it and where can you go
you could almost reversed khaki oak
Akira Fushimi stuck a drummer Steve of a
friend of mine is dying tonight I
expected to die tonight
okay that's when you know it's good to
know where you might go no don't open my
skirt that much tip idea no matter
Chicago I don't but it's an
interesting interesting and I was doing
the courses story and I became very
popular by Adele course a 2002 study of
Tedesco Keane another button and it's
very exotic
it's now Jennings I teach how much in
sexy
friend of mine went crazy / - he was out
questioned in a mental thing I didn't
relax I saw so much Italian English and
Esther there's a cheese and butter she's
that good privately in telling stories
about Russell interestingly that book is
wrong in serious Natasha turkey- not
near a villainous it's the best
technique and Merton and 9/11 the part
of the noble profession that yesterday's
OJC Bardot is a bit that man other is
Easter gift antique source living an
estrogenic of so it's nothing like that
don't even wanna help you it was madness
to at the bottom is cos I destroyed the
Canadian New Year now we don't study it
even is a champion is most always a
chance
I bet that more in Turkey so I thought
at the time yeah two-pointer still
dominate men lose control of the bicep
but I will never sell your stock price
was it by the way what are your options
he is without the once you prove you
choice that I walk away the cars awaits
about the series and of course yeah for
cheetah
people are gonna think am I gonna go I
was operating from a Western over Yahoo
Sharia the coverage Buddha perpetuity
it's the Postal Service Vania CUDA
support péter pápai that you had a
shoulder besides you prove that the COS
alistair here is near to David Caruso
Joseph emotionalism West and cadets
evolved interests material was not a lot
of this course was inspired by my mother
stop yeah because I will send in the
science courses look at my media
vehicles visor of my mama's Balearic
Amano
Dola I went to my mommy yeah personal I
miss cuz cuz I'll pray to that well you
know what you've got meetings oh yeah
good a foul
okay that Shawn and my mom wasn't a
Buddhist and way up mama you're a
Buddhist to me you're both notion in
seriousness and I wrote her yeah I saw a
similar week's mail email of agnostic
that was one session sometimes Indian
male just a nice kiss my pizza so I
wrote her I said you gotta be sorry you
go to be shy we're gonna lose sort of
acid a school she was a school teacher
in the class yeah your study specialist
vitamins and yet said about the police
the other battalion so pretty shy what
are you then you gotta die new be
jealous I was very good I get so I made
a careful and I watched student Balala
the library in the back of a car
but guys native is Lee machine so we put
her in the class I go through a senior
this line unit they taught her for three
months in your vagina base it's a
immediate and I was so impressed
yeah but car that is Sean boy yeah
basically this course came from my own
personal experience I said someday the
course is supporting them open thing
yeah but the most of the vaginal stuff
we do Jim Magali when you might cut
privatization driving that be Sonia
bashed also cheese's or like this could
mean rabbits of course and that's all we
use most well so maybe Dharma and we use
ganden get the dope girl territory
Shekhar simcha man manda I'm gonna
change his name to Tim Amanda
yeah there we go
I also used a book called 10mm Jim what
is it tell them Jim
so the greatest government is more room
to move it's how I submitted a llama
named Jim Moyles allow him to grab a
child in English yes it is extraneous
8,000 pages wasn't disdains if we
translate it yes a bit of aliens not shy
medically and okay and you might be
interested to know he stole the name it
was magic
okay I lost my sister somebody MHN was
at the Venetian tell them to more denim
Jim was in the chat I took up four
elements of the material called the city
a list of children proto in English
means primitive primitive de l'ombre
embrace-toi quadrangle Umbria gamba calm
down 1,000 years ago
this is Angus book ever written by the
comers at the summit imagining a gorilla
and the business like this might hurt
but some facilities needs energy pitch
the switch naked on poetry basically a
rhythm this is the master butcher a
string it's okay this is a thousand
pages at the cellar lumbering Buddhism
is largely crushed in your parish 400
years before it's uncover okay stilettos
I'm not for missing in the world
propeller the King above the Cultural
Revolution when imagination help me Jean
Jean Smith who was Jeff's part for many
years ago we found half of a copy
fleshly people I mean of core people I
see
aikidoka Satya he somehow I ended up in
Indonesia Indonesia became tourism and
your colleagues joined them all together
we may have said mrs. Lillian we printed
it ok so many years ago when I'm reading
from Portugal episode and university
students and he's saying that this is
else famous you get them as no joke you
find this
yeah would you imagine oh yeah
initially he found the only copy on the
show he just looking you go buddy
today is the day I'm gonna be Sinaiticus
him all the invited at the owner user
bridge Thomas whether to stick many
sticks a package of incense hook up one
you light the whole thing when you have
loser guys in monastery of silk scarf
that frequent of Cepheus Fotolia shock
of a sharp any message of Montgomery
Scott snow can be artem word can give
the biggest one
what was about that you you greet a high
Lama if the charity episode of Alamos
with a one give me energy in this
picture it's a but the stability
got nothing to it you don't delicate
alright stubborn I can see you at the
pelagic sharks open deshaney one versus
the Nikita's not a circle on me yeah but
the mustard
put some of that in your hair no that's
illegal rush what is the baby's death in
the realms of existence course so some a
bit of ice course is translated from
there
okay could I see the rooster but if
Anika about three years ago that tree
could nizam high Lama as in the circular
travel Amenia Basilico got this thing
from Tibet you're gonna want it this is
really rare that's cause our stone is
greatest a better term co-founder I see
I printed oh yeah oh yeah yeah
nACCHO crushed almond straight CI father
rabbits and Romania Tosh can you book a
true commercial big rose passivation
okay anyway that's enough dragging
disturb business